

Muhammet Enes Çetin

Nationality: Turkish Date of birth: 2001 Phone number: (+90) 5442817369

Email address: enespcetin@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/muhammet-enes-cetin-35112b279

Website: https://github.com/enesctnn

• Home: (Türkiye)

ABOUT ME

I graduated from Ankara University Computer Programming in 2022. I am currently developing Front End Web applications using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Reactjs and Nextjs14 using TypeScript technologies. You may visit https://github.com/enesctnn for the websites I developed in these languages. Every step I took in the software, every new information I learned and needed to learn, made me even more curious, and I look forward to learning new things. As a Front End Web developer, I love researching and reading documentation. I also have (beginner-intermediate) level knowledge of Adobe's Photoshop, After Effects and Premiere Pro technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Web Developer (INTERNSHIP)

MINISTRY OF AGRICULTURE AND FORESTRY [26/04/2023 - 28/12/2023]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: https://www.ogm.gov.tr/tr

I produced Javascript and React projects under the supervision of Orbis Project manager Ahmet Yatcı at the General Directorate of Agriculture and Forestry also uploaded them on my Github repositories. I had the opportunity to observe teamwork and functioning. Ahmet Yatcı, Tel No: +90 505 864 67 53 . Beştepe, Söğütözü Cd. 8/1, 06560 Yenimahalle/Ankara.

Computer Programming (INTERNSHIP)

Atatürk Forest Farm (AOC) [16/08/2021 – 15/09/2021]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: www.aoc.gov.tr

We provided technical support to AOC employees during internship. We solved problems such as formatting computers, updating/downloading softwares that (completing-correcting) connection between AOC server and the computer and sometimes by replacing the broken cable.

I have experienced a good team work, friendship and partnership under the same roof.

AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN INTERNSHIP

Turkish Aerospace Industries TUSAŞ [10/12/2016 – 13/06/2019]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: https://www.tusas.com

I did an internship at TUSAŞ as an Aircraft Maintenance Technician. My responsibilities were; to support our team for assambling the frame of T-129 Attack Chopper we have faced with couple duties such as combine the pieces with sealant and make sure around of the piece clean at the same time. I also maintained and supply the aircraft pieces such as gearbox and engine cover at Universal Lathe Machine.

DIGITAL SKILLS

Front-End Web Developement / Reactjs Nextjs / Javascript HTML CSS / Good listener and communicator / Adobe (After Effects, Premiere Pro, Photoshop) / Team-work oriented

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Computer Programming

Ankara University [31/08/2020 – 13/06/2022]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: https://www.ankara.edu.tr/dizin/myo/ | Final grade: 3,8/4

Aircraft Airframe, Engine and Maintenance

Private Ankara Darüşşifa Technical Anatolian Vocational School [15/09/2016 – 14/06/2019]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: http://www.darussifa.com.tr/ | Final grade: 82,53/100

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user